[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "R2-D2 and C3-P0 were sold to Ben Kenobi Star Wars: Episode 4.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following months is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "April", "incorrect_answers": ["December", "May", "July"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies was not directed by Woody Allens favorite director, Ingmar Bergman?", "correct_answer": "A Good Marriage", "incorrect_answers": ["The Virgin Spring", "Cries and Whispers", "Wild Strawberries"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about elephants?", "correct_answer": "They are able to digest 40% of their food.", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Their diet consists of 80% tree leaves.", "They spend 8-10 hours a day eating."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following was not a member of the band Lynryd Skynyrd?", "correct_answer": "Jimmy Farrar", "incorrect_answers": ["Gary Rossington", "Allen Collins", "Rickey Medlocke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Plancks constant (h) is equal to this.", "correct_answer": "6.626068 \u00d7 10^(-34) m^2 kg / s", "incorrect_answers": ["1.67262171 x 10^(-27) kg", "1.05457168 x 10^(-34) J s", "10973731.568 525 m^(-1)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These US Presidents - William Henry Harrison, Zachary Taylor, Franklin D. Roosevelt, and Warren G. Harding, all have this in common.", "correct_answer": "They died in office of natural causes.", "incorrect_answers": ["They have been elected without a plurality of popular votes.", "They were all democrats.", "They resigned from office."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The writer and director of Office Space, Mike Judge, made a cameo appearance in the film.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Plaque and bacteria begin to accumulate approximately this long after eating.", "correct_answer": "20 minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["30 minutes", "5 minutes", "60 minutes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What title was considered for the 1991 movie Point Break, co-produced by James Cameron?", "correct_answer": "Riders on the Storm", "incorrect_answers": ["High Tide", "Higher Gliders", "Curbing the Ocean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A beaver will build a dam even in dried up waterways if a recording of rushing water is played.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Fletch, Fletch finds out that Gail Stanwyk is not Alans only wife. Who else is Alan married to?", "correct_answer": "Sally Ann Cavanaugh", "incorrect_answers": ["Peggy Doyle", "Velma Stanwyk", "Kristine Gossman"]}]